

ABOUT ME

Full stack developer with +15 years of design, marketing and advertising experience. Creative and detail oriented with a great capacity to learn and develop new skills. I am a very responsible and proactive team player and will do my best to progress both personally && professionally.

SKILLS

Javascript	••••
HTML	••••
CSS / SASS	00000
React	
Redux	••••
PostgreSQL	••••
Sequelize	••••
Express	••••
Node	••••
Illustrator	
Photoshop	
English	

CONTACT

San Isidro | Bs. As. | Argentina (+54) 9 11 3474 8996 educalo386@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/edua rdo-calo-0a362456/ https://github.com/educalo77

EDUARDO CALO

FULL STACK WEB
DEVELOPER | MKT
SPECIALIST

EDUCATION

HENRY

2020 | BootCamp +700hs of Programming | Full Stack Web Developer

UNIVERSIDAD DE BUENOS AIRES

1997-2005 | Industrial Engineering

ST JOHN'S SCHOOL

1984-1995 | International Baccalaureate. IB & IGCSE

EXPERIENCE

2020 HENRY-APP

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

- App development designed for information management within the Henry community.
- Material-UI, GraphQl, React, Redux, Native, Expo, Javascript. SCRUM & Jira.
- 10/2020-11/2020

2020 ASIAPILAR-SHOES

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- E-commerce
- React, Redux, SASS, Axios, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Express, JWT. SCRUM & Trello
- 09/2020-10/2020

2014- BESTIA GRAFICA & MKT 2020 CORPORATIVA

FOUNDER & OWNER

- Digital printing industry.
- Business planning, assembly and start-up.
- Design, Production & Commercial

2005- WIDE FORMAT

2014 MANAGER PRODUCTION & SALES